alltechfeigames.com 2012-10-02

# 2010 Alltech FEI World Equestrian Games™ - Privacy Policy

### WWW.ALLTECHFEIGAMES.COM PRIVACY POLICY

Thank you for visiting www.alltechfeigames.com, a World Games 2010 Foundation, Inc (“World Games 2010”) Web site. World Games 2010 is committed to providing you an enriching and informative experience within a trusted and secure environment. This privacy policy tells you how WORLD GAMES 2010 uses personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using this Web site or submitting any personal information. By using this site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. We may, infrequently, change these practices, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

The privacy practices set forth in this Privacy Policy are for this Web site only. Other WORLD GAMES 2010 Web sites may have different practices. If you link to other WORLD GAMES 2010 sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites. 

#### What we collect and how we use it 

We will occasionally request information from visitors to provide them special offers and features. In these instances, we collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc. It is only collected when voluntarily submitted by visitors and is only used to fulfill the specific offer or request. For example, to receive email updates or newsletters about the site, the event and promotions; or offer to respond to your question or issue in our contact or email section. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example, to receive future information from us. 

If you have elected to receive future information from us, you may receive information by regular mail or email, depending on the information you provided. From time to time, we may feature products/services from other reputable organizations, companies or brands that may interest you. Your personally identifiable information is not shared with these other companies. All mailings come from WORLD GAMES 2010.

We do not share personally identifiable information collected at this site with third parties, except for the limited instances noted below. The exceptions are: 

We may share your information with our partner agencies who assist us in administering the site and various programs and promotions. They can only use the information to administer our site and programs. These agencies are bound by agreement to keep your information private and secure. 

From time to time we may run a joint promotion on this site with another company or organization. You will always be advised if another company is also collecting information. We recommend you review that company's privacy policy, and we may provide a link to that company's privacy policy. 

Sometimes we run programs featuring another company's service or products and you are given the opportunity to opt-in to future receipt of information from that company. We recommend you review that company's privacy policy, and we may provide a link to that company's privacy policy. 

We may also disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or if in our good faith judgment, such action is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, to respond to any claims, or to protect the rights of WORLD GAMES 2010 and the public. 

In the event of an acquisition of all or part of WORLD GAMES 2010 by another organization, the acquirer would have access to the information maintained by WORLD GAMES 2010, which could include personal information, subject to applicable law. Similarly, information may be transferred as part of a reorganization or insolvency proceeding. WORLD GAMES 2010 may on occasion combine information we receive with outside records to enhance our consumer profiles for our own marketing purposes. 

#### Referrals and prospects

If you send a friend an email from the site referring the friend to the site, the "referral" information you provide is used on a one-time basis to facilitate this communication and is not further retained by WORLD GAMES 2010.   
If you sign a friend up for a special program offered at this site, your friend's information will only be used for the purpose for which provided, and all our communications to your friend contain an opt out.

Cookie/tracking technology  
This site may use cookie and tracking technology. Cookie and tracking technology is useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Web site, and understanding how visitors use the site. Cookies can also help tailor the site to visitors' needs and help customize the site to visitors' requests. For example, we may use cookies to make sure you don't see the same information repeatedly. The site may also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and for other similar purposes. We use general IP address information to better understand how the site is utilized.   
Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate (not individual), cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

#### Information security, opting-out and changing and information

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized WORLD GAMES 2010 employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information and only to help WORLD GAMES 2010 administer its promotional programs and the site. Personally identifiable information is also password protected. 

All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings. You may email us through our Contact Us page to update information, change opt-ins, or request to have your information deleted from our mailing list. You may also use this contact information if you have any questions about this policy or our practices.

#### General

Third party Internet sites accessible through hyperlinks from this site have their own privacy practices, and WORLD GAMES 2010 has no responsibility or liability for these independent practices. Please review their privacy practices for yourself.   
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.

 _\- www.alltechfeigames.com, January 2009_
